me.gr 2003-01-15

# Navel: Privacy policy

**Privacy Policy of "www.navel.gr"**

This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Site and not necessarily to other Navel's sites on the World Wide Web. When leaving this Site, please read the privacy policy applicable to the site you are visiting. **If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site.**

By accessing and using this Site, you hereby agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Non-Personal Information Collected Automatically**

Navel Software Ltd. is committed to the protection of the privacy of its web site visitors. Please note that we may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**Personal Information**

***In order to respond to your questions, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs like Club Navel and Forum Navel, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail, e-mail or phone to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. However,unless compelled by applicable legislation, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs like Club Navel and Forum Navel. You also hereby grant to Navel the right to exchange any information provided by you between Navel's affiliates for the purposes mentioned before.

In addition to the personal information that you may provide us, this Site may use technology that lets us collect certain technical information like your Internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, traffic patterns and the address of any referring Web sites.

**Security**

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet, and no system of technology is completely safe, "tamper" or "hacker- proof", Navel has endeavoured to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of your personal information.

**Accuracy of collected data**

Navel will on its own initiative, or at your request, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by Navel in connection with the operation of this Site. 

**Visitor identification**

From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to allow us to identify you. This information is commonly known as "cookies". By showing how and when our visitors use this Site, this information can help us to continue to improve our Site. We will only use cookies to view information on your hard drive that was put there by a cookie from this Site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many web sites use them. Cookies are stored on your computer and not on this Site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. 

**Minors**

No information may be submitted to Navel by persons under the age of 18 without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, nor may persons under the age of 18 make purchases or other legal acts on this Site without such consent, unless permitted by applicable legislation. 

**Changes**

We may change this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or withdraw access to this Site, or the content of these pages at any time with or without notice.
